So I need y'all to always remember that when you are on this internet, that you are not
controlling what you see.
You do have an algorithm that responds supposedly to what you're interested in.
But the fact of the matter is this platform is a controlled space making decisions about
what messaging reaches whom.
In the current context of the United States carrying out an extrajudicial kidnapping
and attack on a foreign sovereign country for seizure of their resources, you cannot
trust anything you are seeing that supports that.
Even if you see Venezuelans saying, we wanted Maduro out.
Hey, guess what?
Doesn't make it acceptable for the United States to come in.
And the fact of the matter is that there are many Venezuelans who got cut out of the Dallas
when Chavez came in, as well as Maduro, his successor.
And so their families are still mad that they are no longer living high off the hog.
High on the hog?
I think it's high on the hog.
High on the hog.
So just like Marco Rubio's posh Spaniard Cuban family is still mad that Fidel came in and
said, no more of that.
You're going to see Venezuelans who are saying the same thing.
So you who consider yourself a humanist, who consider yourself someone who wants to see
collective liberation, who wants to see the fall of corporatism, of imperialism, and of empire.
You cannot in any way support those who are supporting what is happening today via the U.S.
government.
It is unlawful, it is theft, and it is colonialism.
You cannot in any way support those who want to see the U.S.
The U.S. government.
Camina, camina, camina y seguiremos lucha y batalla.
Estamos unidos en esta situación que tenemos y estamos alegres por la unidad, o sea, porque
estamos unidos, pero también estamos en esa unión para ir también para defender nuestra
patria, defenderla y defender nuestra riqueza.
Estamos unidos, pero también estamos alegres por la confidencia.
¡Gracias por ver mi énata!